So, the opinion would be to buy in ICICI GI, IC Labad.
We were seeing consolidation for the past few days but
if we look at yesterday's pattern on closing basis, then
it is a breakout case. A little
better volume was seen there, so I
think after this breakout you can see a smart
move. I think
you can buy here even at the current level
and
your stop loss will be at 1464 and
your target will be at 15.
If you want to take a trade in options in ICICI GI, then the
call option of 1500 for the month of December can be
taken. The closing was around 38,
so you should buy there,
put a stop loss of 8 and a target of 0.
In this option also, ok ICICI GI,
ICCI Labad, you have to do buying here,
this is a minus pick, so one defense share,
one insurance share. Till now Rajesh ji, good
morning